boostcruising.com 2011-07-23

# Boostcruising - Boostcruising.com - Terms and Conditions

Boostcruising is committed to protecting your privacy in accordance with the National Privacy Principles set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). Those principles regulate the way in which we collect, use, store, disclose and provide access to your personal information.

This Privacy Policy explains certain aspects of how we have implemented the National Privacy Principles in order to protect the privacy of your personal information.

**Personal Information:**

Personal information is information that allows others to identify you.

If you become a member of Boostcruising.com the personal information about you which is collected and held :

\- will include your name, gender, email address, height and date of birth as well as details of our services which you have used and statistics on usage;

\- may include your current address, telephone numbers, mobile phone numbers, bank account or credit card details, ethnicity, religion, education and other information you voluntarily provide either in registering as a member of Boostcruising.com or in content which you post to this website.

Whether you are a visitor to our website or a Boostcruising.com member there may also be information which we automatically record but does not personally identify you such as your internet service provider and top level domain, the date and time at which you access our website, the web pages accessed and the browser software you are using.

**How we collect personal information:**

Personal information is information that allows others to identify you.

If you become a member of Boostcruising.com the personal information about you which is collected and held:

\- will include your name, gender, email address, height and date of birth as well as details of our services which you have used and statistics on usage;

\- may include your current address, telephone numbers, mobile phone numbers, bank account or credit card details, ethnicity, religion, education and other information you voluntarily provide either in registering as a member of Boostcruising.com or in content which you post to this website.

Whether you are a visitor to our website or a Boostcruising.com member there may also be information which we automatically record but does not personally identify you such as your internet service provider and top level domain, the date and time at which you access our website, the web pages accessed and the browser software you are using.

**How we use your personal information:**

Your personal information may be used in order to:

\- provide the Boostcruising.com services to you;

\- assist you with any questions you may have regarding the use of those services;

\- administer and manage those services, including charging, billing and collecting debts;

\- inform you of new or other services or products which we provide, unless you tell us that you do not want such information;

\- take appropriate measures to detect and prevent fraud and credit loss;

\- monitor, evaluate, research and develop our services;

\- gain an understanding of our members and their needs in order to provide a better service.

**What happens if you do not provide all or a part of the personal information requested:**

If you do not provide all or a part of the required information for registration as a member of Boostcruising.com, we are unable to register you as a member of Boostcruising.com and you will be unable to enjoy the benefits of membership.

**When we disclose your personal information:**

We respect your privacy and for this reason we do not engage in the trading or alternative unauthorised use of your personal information. However there will be occasions on which we disclose your personal information to other organisations. The organisations to which we disclose information may include:

\- government and regulatory authorities, law enforcement agencies and other organisations as required or authorised by law;

\- fraud investigation agencies;

\- credit providers for credit related purposes such as credit checks;

\- an organisation involved in the sale or transfer of our business;

\- our related companies but only for the same purposes for which we are entitled to use your personal information.

**Posting content on our website:**

Information included in any member profile which is posted to this website is as a result of the member's specific request that such information be posted. All information which you provide when you post your profile to our website will be accessible by anyone who accesses the internet. Anyone who visits our website may access, download and print any information which you include in your posted profile. We are not responsible for the use or disclosure by others of the information included in your posted profile.

You have the option at any time to remove any information which you have previously included in your posted profile.

**Your consent:**

We will assume that you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as detailed above unless you tell us otherwise.

**Your right of access to your personal information:**

You have a right to access your personal information, subject to some exceptions allowed by the National Privacy Principles. If you would like to be provided with access to the personal information about you which we hold, please contact us.

If we refuse to provide you with access to the information which you have requested, we will provide you with the reasons for the refusal and any exceptions on which we rely on under the National Privacy Principles.

We are entitled to charge a reasonable fee for allowing you access to your personal information.

**Help us to ensure we hold accurate information:**

We take all reasonable precautions to ensure that the personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up to date. However, the accuracy of that information depends to a large extent on the information you provide.

If the personal information which we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date, please contact us and we will take reasonable steps to correct the information which we hold or discuss with you appropriate alternative action.

It is important that you keep us up to date with changes to personal information such as your name, mailing address and email address.

**Links:**

This website may contain links to other websites which are not operated by Boostcruising. We cannot guarantee that any personal information which you provide to those websites will be protected by the same privacy practices which we employ. For this reason before you provide any personal information to a linked website, please carefully read and be satisfied with that website's privacy policy.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy:**

We may alter this Privacy Policy from time to time in accordance with legal requirements or to meet our business requirements. Any alterations to our Privacy Policy will be reflected on this website.

©2011 Boostcruising.  
All rights reserved.
